<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mysql on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mysql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mysql on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mysql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining JKN Data in Bojonegoro: How I Built the CEKATAN App with CodeIgniter and MySQL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</guid>
      <description>As a Full Stack Developer at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the exciting opportunity to dive into a game-changing project: CEKATAN. This web application, crafted entirely by yours truly using CodeIgniter 3 and MySQL, was developed from November to December 2023.
So, what’s CEKATAN all about?
CEKATAN is designed to verify and validate BPJS (Badan Penyelenggara Jaminan Sosial) participant data in Bojonegoro Regency. With this app, we ensure that JKN participant data is spot on, making the JKN program management smoother and more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Gen Stakeholder Solutions: How SIMONA BIDUAN Redefines Complaint Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</guid>
      <description>At PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the exciting opportunity to develop a cutting-edge web application: Sistem Monitoring Pelayanan Bidang Informasi dan Pengaduan Stakeholders (SIMONA BIDUAN). This project was designed to tackle the challenges of managing stakeholder complaints for the Ministry of Law and Human Rights of the Republic of Indonesia (Kemenkumham RI).
What Was the Problem? Kemenkumham RI faced several issues in managing stakeholder complaints:
No Central Hub: Complaints were managed through disjointed systems, making tracking and management challenging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever craved a warm plate of fried rice on a cold night but felt too lazy to leave the house? Or wanted to try out new dishes from your favorite restaurant without having to wait in line?
Ordera is here to meet your needs!
Why You’ll Love Ordera Ordera is a rising food and beverage delivery application in Indonesia. This app offers several advantages that make it a must-try:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting the PELANGI App: Advancing Towards a Smarter Ngasem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</guid>
      <description>PELANGI (short for Pelayanan Ngasem Terintegrasi) is here to make life in Ngasem easier and more connected. Launched in 2023, this app is all about streamlining access and offering smart solutions for the community.
&amp;ldquo;PELANGI is crafted to improve the quality of life for Ngasem residents and boost the connection between the government and its people using the latest in digital tech.&amp;rdquo;
Check Out PELANGI&amp;rsquo;s Cool Features Feature Description Administrative Registration Easily register for essential documents like KTP, KK, and more right from the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>December 11, 2020, is a day I&amp;rsquo;ll always remember. On that date, I successfully passed the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This exam marked an important initial step in my journey toward becoming a proficient database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
