<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mysql on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mysql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mysql on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mysql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Verifying JKN Data in Bojonegoro with CodeIgniter and MySQL: Developing the CEKATAN Application</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</guid>
      <description>Delving into the World of JKN Data Verification As a Full Stack Developer at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the opportunity to contribute to a meaningful project: building the Cek dan Validasi Data JKN Kabupaten Bojonegoro (CEKATAN) web application. This project ran from November to December 2023, and I am proud to have designed and built this application independently using the CodeIgniter 3 framework and the MySQL database.
What is CEKATAN?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovative Stakeholder Engagement: Simona Biduan&#39;s Complaint Management System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</guid>
      <description>Delving into the Challenges of Stakeholder Complaint Management As a Full Stack Developer at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the opportunity to contribute to the development of an innovative web application: Sistem Monitoring Pelayanan Bidang Informasi dan Pengaduan Stakeholders (SIMONA BIDUAN).
SIMONA BIDUAN emerged as a comprehensive software solution to manage and track stakeholder complaints, particularly within the Ministry of Law and Human Rights of the Republic of Indonesia (Kemenkumham RI).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Ordera: Delivering Delicious Food to Your Doorstep! Have you ever craved a warm plate of fried rice on a cold night but felt too lazy to leave the house? Or wanted to try out new dishes from your favorite restaurant without having to wait in line?
Ordera is here to meet your needs!
Ordera: What Makes It Special? Ordera is a rising food and beverage delivery application in Indonesia. This app offers several advantages that make it a must-try:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting the PELANGI App: Advancing Towards a Smarter Ngasem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</guid>
      <description>Overview PELANGI, short for Pelayanan Ngasem Terintegrasi, is a digital platform designed to deliver a seamless experience for the people of Ngasem. Launched in 2023, this app is all about making access easier and providing smart solutions to meet the diverse needs and demands of the community.
&amp;ldquo;PELANGI is designed to enhance the quality of life for Ngasem residents and strengthen the bond between the government and its citizens through the power of digital technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>December 11, 2020, is a day I&amp;rsquo;ll always remember. On that date, I successfully passed the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This exam marked an important initial step in my journey toward becoming a proficient database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
