<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Charting My Cyber Security Path: A Collection of Courses and Certifications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! Welcome to my cyber security collection. If you’re here, you probably share a love for all things tech and security like I do. Over time, I&amp;rsquo;ve dived into various courses and earned certifications that have shaped my journey in cyber security. Below is a showcase of what I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished so far, along with the skills I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up along the way.
Why Cyber Security? Let’s face it—cyber threats aren’t going anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Cyber Attacks Unfold: Set Up T-Pot Honeypot on Google Cloud Platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/deploying-tpot-honeypot-on-gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/deploying-tpot-honeypot-on-gcp/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to explore security and dive into honeypot analysis, T-Pot is a fantastic tool that consolidates multiple honeypots into one robust platform. Today, I’ll guide you step-by-step through deploying T-Pot on Google Cloud Platform (GCP). By the end, you’ll have a fully operational T-Pot honeypot ready to capture and visualize attack data.
What is T-Pot? T-Pot, developed by T-Mobile, is an all-in-one honeypot platform supporting over 20 honeypots. It includes features like animated attack maps, visualization through Elastic Stack, and a suite of tools for enhanced threat analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Your New Application on OpenResty Edge: An Easy-to-Follow Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome aboard! If you’re gearing up to launch a new application on OpenResty Edge, you’re in the right place. Whether you’re a seasoned pro or just starting out, I’ll walk you through every step of the way with a dash of fun. Grab your favorite drink, settle in, and let’s dive into this setup adventure!
Creating Your New Application Let&amp;rsquo;s get that new app live and kicking in no time. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to create your first application on OpenResty Edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Ahead of Issues: How to Connect Grafana Alerts with Slack and Jira Using n8n</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</guid>
      <description>So, you’re ready to up your game and make sure you never miss a critical update? Great choice! Setting up Grafana alerts and integrating them with Slack and Jira through n8n is a powerful way to keep your team on the ball. Let’s dive in and get those workflows automated!
Setting Up Grafana Alerts First up, let’s get your Grafana alerts configured so you’re always in the know. Here’s the lowdown on how to get your alerts up and running:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Gophish on Google Cloud Platform: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a simple, powerful, and free tool to simulate phishing attacks and train your team on cybersecurity, then Gophish is your go-to solution! This open-source phishing framework allows you to easily manage phishing campaigns, helping to improve security awareness without breaking the bank.
What is Gophish? Gophish is a powerful open-source phishing framework designed to make the process of conducting and managing phishing campaigns as straightforward as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Alerts to Malware: A CyberOps Associates v1.0 Skill Assessment Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-v1-0-skills-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-v1-0-skills-assessment/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered what security analysts actually do? Buckle up, because we&amp;rsquo;re diving into a thrilling investigation of a malware attack! Today&amp;rsquo;s culprit? The notorious Pushdo trojan.
This post will take you through a simulated security assessment, mimicking the thought process and steps involved in uncovering malicious activity. We&amp;rsquo;ll dissect alerts, explore the tools used for analysis, and ultimately expose the tricks employed by Pushdo.
So, grab a cup of coffee (or your beverage of choice), and let&amp;rsquo;s embark on this malware takedown adventure!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Like a Pro: A Beginner’s Guide to Vulnhub&#39;s Basic Pentesting 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to test your penetration testing skills in a safe environment? Look no further than Vulnhub’s Basic Pentesting 1 machine! This virtual machine is designed specifically for beginners, offering a controlled space to learn the ropes of exploiting vulnerabilities and gaining access.
In this guide, I’ll walk you through the thrilling journey of taking down Vulnhub&amp;rsquo;s Basic Pentesting 1, step-by-step. So, grab your tools and get ready to unleash your inner hacker (for good, of course)!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Code: My Experience with Malware Analysis at Protergo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</guid>
      <description>If you’re interested in malware analysis, using Cuckoo Sandbox is an exciting and safe way to dissect potentially malicious files. During my technical interview at Protergo, I had the opportunity to showcase my skills by analyzing a suspicious file. In this blog post, I’ll walk you through the process I followed using Cuckoo Sandbox, a powerful tool for both static and dynamic analysis.
What is Cuckoo Sandbox? Cuckoo Sandbox is an open-source automated malware analysis system that allows you to analyze malware in an isolated environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining JKN Data in Bojonegoro: How I Built the CEKATAN App with CodeIgniter and MySQL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered how tech can transform data verification? Enter CEKATAN—a web application I had the privilege to bring to life. Built with CodeIgniter 3 and MySQL over a whirlwind couple of months (November–December 2023), CEKATAN is here to tackle the complexities of BPJS (Badan Penyelenggara Jaminan Sosial) participant data in Bojonegoro Regency.
Let’s dive into what makes CEKATAN a game-changer.
What’s CEKATAN All About? CEKATAN (short for Cek dan Validasi Data JKN Kabupaten Bojonegoro) is your go-to solution for verifying and validating JKN participant data with ease and precision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Gen Stakeholder Solutions: How SIMONA BIDUAN Redefines Complaint Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</guid>
      <description>Imagine dealing with a flood of complaints every day without a clear system to organize, track, or resolve them. That was the challenge for Kemenkumham RI (Ministry of Law and Human Rights, Indonesia). Complaints were piling up in scattered systems, manual processes slowed things down, and stakeholders had no clue about the status of their issues.
That’s where SIMONA BIDUAN (short for Sistem Monitoring Pelayanan Bidang Informasi dan Pengaduan Stakeholders) comes in—a web application I had the opportunity to create from scratch between September and November 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Ever had those cozy nights where all you want is a warm plate of fried rice, but leaving the house feels like a mission? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re dreaming of trying new dishes from your favorite restaurants—minus the wait.
Say hello to Ordera!
Ordera is Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s rising star in food and beverage delivery, here to make your dining experience effortless and exciting.
Why You’ll Love Ordera Ordera is a rising food and beverage delivery application in Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting the PELANGI App: Advancing Towards a Smarter Ngasem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</guid>
      <description>Say hello to PELANGI (short for Pelayanan Ngasem Terintegrasi)—a game-changing app that’s here to make living in Ngasem easier, faster, and more connected. Launched in 2023, PELANGI is all about simplifying access to essential services and building stronger connections between the community and local government.
“PELANGI is designed to enhance everyday life for Ngasem residents while creating a transparent and seamless bridge between the people and their government—all powered by cutting-edge digital tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Campus Life: How SITERPADU Transforms Academic Administration at Universitas Jenderal Achmad Yani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sistem-terintegrasi-pengelolaan-sumber-daya-unjani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sistem-terintegrasi-pengelolaan-sumber-daya-unjani/</guid>
      <description>Hey, tech enthusiasts! Today, I want to share an exciting chapter in my development journey: working on the SITERPADU application. This project, which spanned all of 2022, was an incredible opportunity to dive deep into the world of full-stack development while creating something that truly makes a difference in academic administration.
What’s SITERPADU All About? SITERPADU (short for Sistem Terintegrasi Pengelolaan Sumber Daya Universitas Jenderal Achmad Yani) is an online platform designed to simplify and streamline administrative processes for the university.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>On December 11, 2020, I took an important step in my tech career by passing the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This milestone marked the beginning of my journey toward becoming a skilled database administrator, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more excited to share what I learned along the way.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? The MTA Database Administration Fundamentals certification is designed to test your basic knowledge and skills in database management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a COVID-19 WebGIS Application: Unforgettable Internship Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</guid>
      <description>In 2020, I had the chance to contribute to an impactful project: building the COVID-19 WebGIS application. The goal was simple but important—creating a web platform that helps people understand the pandemic situation in Indonesia through maps, charts, and data analysis.
What’s COVID-19 WebGIS? It&amp;rsquo;s a web-based application that provides a visual representation of COVID-19 data in Indonesia. Users can view real-time stats, including case numbers, recoveries, and deaths, all displayed on interactive maps and easy-to-read charts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
