<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Securing Cyberspace: A Dive into Ethical Hacker Training with Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ethical-hacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ethical-hacker/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my blog! The digital world is rapidly evolving, opening up new opportunities while also presenting increasingly complex cybersecurity risks. On March 29, 2024, I completed the Ethical Hacker course from Cisco Networking Academy, a significant step in my journey to becoming a hero in this challenging digital landscape.
What is Ethical Hacking? Ethical hacking is the practice of learning and applying hacking techniques used by malicious hackers, but with the noble purpose of finding and fixing system vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Kickstarted My Career in Cybersecurity: A Sharing Session with Merdeka Siber Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-kick-starting-career-into-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-kick-starting-career-into-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my experience attending the &amp;ldquo;How To Kick Starting Career Into Cyber Security&amp;rdquo; sharing session hosted by Merdeka Siber Academy on March 24, 2024. This insightful session provided me with valuable knowledge about the fundamentals of SOC Analyst roles and the exciting prospects of career shifting into cybersecurity.
Stepping into the World of Cybersecurity As an individual with a keen interest in technology and a passion for problem-solving, I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by the ever-evolving realm of cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conquering Vulnhub&#39;s Basic Pentesting 1: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</guid>
      <description>Overview Have you ever wanted to test your penetration testing skills in a safe environment? Look no further than Vulnhub&amp;rsquo;s Basic Pentesting 1 machine! This virtual machine is designed specifically for beginners like me, offering a controlled space to learn the ropes of exploiting vulnerabilities and gaining access.
In this guide, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the thrilling journey of taking down Basic Pentesting 1, step-by-step. So, grab your tools and get ready to unleash your inner hacker (for good, of course)!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Digital Landscape: An Introduction to Cybersecurity with Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s hyperconnected world, cybersecurity has become an indispensable skill, not just for tech professionals but for everyone navigating the digital landscape. With the ever-evolving nature of cyber threats, understanding the fundamentals of cybersecurity is crucial to safeguard our personal and professional lives.
Embarking on the Cybersecurity Path My fascination with cybersecurity led me to enroll in Cisco Networking Academy&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Cybersecurity course on February 28, 2024. This comprehensive course provided a solid foundation in the world of cybersecurity, equipping me with the knowledge and skills to navigate the digital frontier with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Security: Achieving Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) with The SecOps Group</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>February 13, 2024 marked a significant milestone in my professional journey as I successfully passed the Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) exam from The SecOps Group. This certification validates my expertise in application security, a field that has become increasingly critical in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
What is CAP? The CAP certification is a highly sought-after credential in the cybersecurity industry. It recognizes individuals who possess the knowledge and skills necessary to secure applications throughout their development lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security Exploration: Unveiling the Path to Becoming a Pentester and Bug Hunter with SanberCode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bug-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bug-hunter/</guid>
      <description>From Zero to Cyber Security Hero in One Month It&amp;rsquo;s been a whirlwind of a month, but I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I&amp;rsquo;ve just completed an intensive Cyber Security Bootcamp at SanberCode! This program was designed to transform individuals with no prior experience into skilled penetration testers and bug hunters. And let me tell you, it was an incredible journey.
What I Learned The bootcamp covered a wide range of topics, including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening Cyber Defenses: My Growth with ITBOX&#39;s Cybersecurity Courses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-security-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-security-courses/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered how those hackers manage to break into secure systems and steal valuable data? Or perhaps you&amp;rsquo;re fascinated by the intricate world of cybersecurity and want to learn how to protect yourself from online threats? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently embarked on an exciting journey into the realm of cybersecurity, and I&amp;rsquo;m here to share my experience with you.
Embarking on the Cybersecurity Path My cybersecurity adventure began on January 02, 2024, when I enrolled in the Cyber Security Course Level Basic from ITBOX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Code: My Experience with Malware Analysis at Protergo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</guid>
      <description>During my technical interview at Protergo, I had the opportunity to showcase my skills in malware analysis. This blog post will take you through the exciting journey of dissecting a suspicious file using Cuckoo Sandbox, a powerful tool for both static and dynamic analysis.
Step-by-Step Malware Analysis with Cuckoo Sandbox Unpacking the Suspect After downloading the sample file, I unzipped it to reveal its contents. This initial step allows us to see what&amp;rsquo;s lurking inside the archive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying JKN Data in Bojonegoro with CodeIgniter and MySQL: Developing the CEKATAN Application</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</guid>
      <description>Delving into the World of JKN Data Verification As a Full Stack Developer at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the opportunity to contribute to a meaningful project: building the Cek dan Validasi Data JKN Kabupaten Bojonegoro (CEKATAN) web application. This project ran from November to December 2023, and I am proud to have designed and built this application independently using the CodeIgniter 3 framework and the MySQL database.
What is CEKATAN?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovative Stakeholder Engagement: Simona Biduan&#39;s Complaint Management System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</guid>
      <description>Delving into the Challenges of Stakeholder Complaint Management As a Full Stack Developer at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the opportunity to contribute to the development of an innovative web application: Sistem Monitoring Pelayanan Bidang Informasi dan Pengaduan Stakeholders (SIMONA BIDUAN).
SIMONA BIDUAN emerged as a comprehensive software solution to manage and track stakeholder complaints, particularly within the Ministry of Law and Human Rights of the Republic of Indonesia (Kemenkumham RI).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Ordera: Delivering Delicious Food to Your Doorstep! Have you ever craved a warm plate of fried rice on a cold night but felt too lazy to leave the house? Or wanted to try out new dishes from your favorite restaurant without having to wait in line?
Ordera is here to meet your needs!
Ordera: What Makes It Special? Ordera is a rising food and beverage delivery application in Indonesia. This app offers several advantages that make it a must-try:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting the PELANGI App: Advancing Towards a Smarter Ngasem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</guid>
      <description>Overview PELANGI, short for Pelayanan Ngasem Terintegrasi, is a digital platform designed to deliver a seamless experience for the people of Ngasem. Launched in 2023, this app is all about making access easier and providing smart solutions to meet the diverse needs and demands of the community.
&amp;ldquo;PELANGI is designed to enhance the quality of life for Ngasem residents and strengthen the bond between the government and its citizens through the power of digital technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Academic Administration at Universitas Jenderal Achmad Yani: Leveraging SITERPADU Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sistem-terintegrasi-pengelolaan-sumber-daya-unjani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sistem-terintegrasi-pengelolaan-sumber-daya-unjani/</guid>
      <description>Overview Greetings, fellow tech enthusiasts! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share my journey as a Full Stack Developer at Bandung Techno Park, where I had the privilege of contributing to the development of the SITERPADU application. This project, spanning from January 1, 2022, to December 31, 2022, provided me with invaluable hands-on experience and a deeper understanding of the intricacies of full-stack development.
Delving into SITERPADU: A Comprehensive Academic Management System SITERPADU stands as a testament to the power of technology in streamlining academic administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>December 11, 2020, is a day I&amp;rsquo;ll always remember. On that date, I successfully passed the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This exam marked an important initial step in my journey toward becoming a proficient database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a COVID-19 WebGIS Application: Unforgettable Internship Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</guid>
      <description>June - July 2020
Interning at PT Sketsa Negeri Mandiri in 2020 was no ordinary experience. Alongside one team member, I had the opportunity to contribute to an important project: building the COVID-19 WebGIS application.
What is COVID-19 WebGIS? Imagine an online platform displaying COVID-19 data in Indonesia visually, complete with maps, charts, and analysis. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s the COVID-19 WebGIS, a web-based application that helps users understand the pandemic situation better.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
