<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Security: My Journey to Becoming a Certified AppSec Practitioner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Join me on a thrilling journey as I unveil my triumph in achieving the prestigious Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) certification from The SecOpsGroup. From the initial challenges to the victorious outcome, this blog post encapsulates my expedition towards mastering the art of application security.
1. The Genesis of My Journey Delve into the inception of my aspiration towards becoming an AppSec Practitioner (CAP). Explore the motivations and inspirations that fueled my determination to embark on this remarkable voyage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Overview Ordera, the brainchild of innovative minds at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, has transformed the way Indonesians experience food delivery. In this blog post, I delve into the journey of creating Ordera, an app that not only connects users with their favorite eateries but also revolutionizes the food delivery landscape in Indonesia.
Building Ordera: A Journey of Innovation In the bustling world of food delivery apps, Ordera stands out as a beacon of convenience and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SITERPADU Unleashed: My Odyssey as a Full Stack Developer at Bandung Techno Park</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/siterpadu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/siterpadu/</guid>
      <description>Overview Hey, tech enthusiasts! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to guide you through an electrifying expedition during my tenure as a Full Stack Developer at Bandung Techno Park. Brace yourselves as we plunge into the dynamic world of SITERPADU, the groundbreaking platform reshaping academic administration at Universitas Jenderal Achmad Yani. Join me as I narrate the captivating tale of revolutionizing graduation procedures within the formidable framework of SITERPADU.
Embracing the Challenge At the dawn of 2022, I found myself at the forefront of innovation, poised to tackle the challenges ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Database Administration: My Journey to Certification</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Overview Hey, fellow tech enthusiasts! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share a significant milestone in my career journey - achieving certification in Database Administration Fundamentals from Microsoft Technology Associate. Buckle up as I take you through my exhilarating ride of mastering the world of database administration.
Embarking on the Journey It all began with a burning curiosity to delve deeper into the intricate world of databases. With a thirst for knowledge, I eagerly enrolled in a comprehensive training program aimed at equipping enthusiasts like me with the essential skills needed to conquer the realm of database administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Making of COVID-19 WebGIS: A Journey in Digital Mapping and Visual Storytelling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</guid>
      <description>In the fast-paced world of tech, the development of applications often reflects the urgency of the times. My stint as a Web Developer intern at PT Sketsa Negeri Mandiri thrust me into the heart of this narrative, where alongside a dynamic duo, I embarked on a mission to contribute to the fight against COVID-19 through digital innovation.
The Genesis: Taking Over the Baton Embarking on this project in the midst of a global pandemic was akin to stepping into a whirlwind.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
