<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Charting My Cyber Security Path: A Collection of Courses and Certifications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! Welcome to my cyber security collection. If you’re here, you probably share a love for all things tech and security like I do. Over time, I&amp;rsquo;ve dived into various courses and earned certifications that have shaped my journey in cyber security. Below is a showcase of what I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished so far, along with the skills I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up along the way.
Why Cyber Security? Let’s face it—cyber threats aren’t going anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Your New Application on OpenResty Edge: An Easy-to-Follow Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome aboard! If you’re gearing up to launch a new application on OpenResty Edge, you’re in the right place. Whether you’re a seasoned pro or just starting out, I’ll walk you through every step of the way with a dash of fun. Grab your favorite drink, settle in, and let’s dive into this setup adventure!
Creating Your New Application Let&amp;rsquo;s get that new app live and kicking in no time. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to create your first application on OpenResty Edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Ahead of Issues: How to Connect Grafana Alerts with Slack and Jira Using n8n</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</guid>
      <description>So, you’re ready to up your game and make sure you never miss a critical update? Great choice! Setting up Grafana alerts and integrating them with Slack and Jira through n8n is a powerful way to keep your team on the ball. Let’s dive in and get those workflows automated!
Setting Up Grafana Alerts First up, let’s get your Grafana alerts configured so you’re always in the know. Here’s the lowdown on how to get your alerts up and running:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Gophish on Google Cloud Platform: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</guid>
      <description>What is Gophish? Gophish is a powerful open-source phishing framework designed to make the process of conducting and managing phishing campaigns as straightforward as possible. Think of it as your go-to tool for simulating real-world phishing attacks. The best part? It&amp;rsquo;s free and easy to use!
Affordable: Gophish is open-source software, which means you don&amp;rsquo;t have to pay a cent to use it. Accessible: Written in the Go programming language, Gophish releases are compiled binaries with no dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Alerts to Malware: A CyberOps Associates v1.0 Skill Assessment Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-v1-0-skills-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-v1-0-skills-assessment/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered what security analysts actually do? Buckle up, because we&amp;rsquo;re diving into a thrilling investigation of a malware attack! Today&amp;rsquo;s culprit? The notorious Pushdo trojan.
This post will take you through a simulated security assessment, mimicking the thought process and steps involved in uncovering malicious activity. We&amp;rsquo;ll dissect alerts, explore the tools used for analysis, and ultimately expose the tricks employed by Pushdo.
So, grab a cup of coffee (or your beverage of choice), and let&amp;rsquo;s embark on this malware takedown adventure!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Like a Pro: A Beginner’s Guide to Vulnhub&#39;s Basic Pentesting 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to test your penetration testing skills in a safe environment? Look no further than Vulnhub&amp;rsquo;s Basic Pentesting 1 machine! This virtual machine is designed specifically for beginners like me, offering a controlled space to learn the ropes of exploiting vulnerabilities and gaining access.
In this guide, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the thrilling journey of taking down Basic Pentesting 1, step-by-step. So, grab your tools and get ready to unleash your inner hacker (for good, of course)!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Code: My Experience with Malware Analysis at Protergo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</guid>
      <description>During my technical interview at Protergo, I had the opportunity to showcase my skills in malware analysis. This blog post will take you through the exciting journey of dissecting a suspicious file using Cuckoo Sandbox, a powerful tool for both static and dynamic analysis.
Step-by-Step Malware Analysis with Cuckoo Sandbox Step 1: Unpacking the Suspect After downloading the sample file, I unzipped it to reveal its contents. This initial step allows us to see what&amp;rsquo;s lurking inside the archive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining JKN Data in Bojonegoro: How I Built the CEKATAN App with CodeIgniter and MySQL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cek-dan-validasi-data-jkn/</guid>
      <description>As a Full Stack Developer at PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the exciting opportunity to dive into a game-changing project: CEKATAN. This web application, crafted entirely by yours truly using CodeIgniter 3 and MySQL, was developed from November to December 2023.
So, what’s CEKATAN all about?
CEKATAN is designed to verify and validate BPJS (Badan Penyelenggara Jaminan Sosial) participant data in Bojonegoro Regency. With this app, we ensure that JKN participant data is spot on, making the JKN program management smoother and more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Gen Stakeholder Solutions: How SIMONA BIDUAN Redefines Complaint Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/simona-biduan/</guid>
      <description>At PT Motiolabs Digital Indonesia, I had the exciting opportunity to develop a cutting-edge web application: Sistem Monitoring Pelayanan Bidang Informasi dan Pengaduan Stakeholders (SIMONA BIDUAN). This project was designed to tackle the challenges of managing stakeholder complaints for the Ministry of Law and Human Rights of the Republic of Indonesia (Kemenkumham RI).
What Was the Problem? Kemenkumham RI faced several issues in managing stakeholder complaints:
No Central Hub: Complaints were managed through disjointed systems, making tracking and management challenging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever craved a warm plate of fried rice on a cold night but felt too lazy to leave the house? Or wanted to try out new dishes from your favorite restaurant without having to wait in line?
Ordera is here to meet your needs!
Why You’ll Love Ordera Ordera is a rising food and beverage delivery application in Indonesia. This app offers several advantages that make it a must-try:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting the PELANGI App: Advancing Towards a Smarter Ngasem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pelayanan-ngasem-terintegrasi/</guid>
      <description>PELANGI (short for Pelayanan Ngasem Terintegrasi) is here to make life in Ngasem easier and more connected. Launched in 2023, this app is all about streamlining access and offering smart solutions for the community.
&amp;ldquo;PELANGI is crafted to improve the quality of life for Ngasem residents and boost the connection between the government and its people using the latest in digital tech.&amp;rdquo;
Check Out PELANGI&amp;rsquo;s Cool Features Feature Description Administrative Registration Easily register for essential documents like KTP, KK, and more right from the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Campus Life: How SITERPADU Transforms Academic Administration at Universitas Jenderal Achmad Yani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sistem-terintegrasi-pengelolaan-sumber-daya-unjani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sistem-terintegrasi-pengelolaan-sumber-daya-unjani/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, fellow tech enthusiasts! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share my journey as a Full Stack Developer at Bandung Techno Park, where I had the privilege of contributing to the development of the SITERPADU application. This project, spanning from January 1, 2022, to December 31, 2022, provided me with invaluable hands-on experience and a deeper understanding of the intricacies of full-stack development.
What’s SITERPADU All About? SITERPADU stands as a testament to the power of technology in streamlining academic administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>On December 11, 2020, I took a significant step in my tech journey by passing the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This achievement marked the start of my quest to become a skilled database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:
Topic Description Basic database concepts Understanding database structure and terminology Database creation and management Creating, managing, and maintaining databases Database security Implementing security measures to protect databases Troubleshooting and problem-solving Identifying and resolving database issues Why Did I Pursue This Certification?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a COVID-19 WebGIS Application: Unforgettable Internship Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</guid>
      <description>Interning at PT Sketsa Negeri Mandiri in 2020 was no ordinary experience. Alongside one team member, I had the opportunity to contribute to an important project: building the COVID-19 WebGIS application.
What’s COVID-19 WebGIS? Imagine an online platform displaying COVID-19 data in Indonesia visually, complete with maps, charts, and analysis. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s the COVID-19 WebGIS, a web-based application that helps users understand the pandemic situation better.
Tech and Challenges This application leverages advanced technology, including:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
