<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Security: My Journey to Becoming a Certified AppSec Practitioner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Join me on a thrilling journey as I unveil my triumph in achieving the prestigious Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) certification from The SecOpsGroup. From the initial challenges to the victorious outcome, this blog post encapsulates my expedition towards mastering the art of application security.
1. The Genesis of My Journey Delve into the inception of my aspiration towards becoming an AppSec Practitioner (CAP). Explore the motivations and inspirations that fueled my determination to embark on this remarkable voyage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s vibrant culinary scene, convenience and choice are essential elements that shape the dining experience. Ordera emerges as a beacon of convenience, offering a comprehensive food and beverage delivery platform that caters to the diverse tastes of Indonesian consumers. With an extensive network of registered restaurants and food stalls, Ordera sets the standard for hassle-free dining solutions.
Understanding Ordera Ordera represents more than just a food delivery app; it&amp;rsquo;s a culinary ecosystem designed to simplify and enhance the way Indonesians enjoy their favorite meals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building SITERPADU Academic Information System for UNJANI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/siterpadu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/siterpadu/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the dynamic realm of modern academia, the effectiveness of administrative systems plays a pivotal role in shaping the quality of education and the overall student experience. Jenderal Achmad Yani University has embarked on a transformative journey by integrating SITERPADU, an innovative online academic administration system. Among its array of modules, the Graduation module stands out as a pinnacle of streamlined administrative processes, specifically tailored to address the complexities associated with student graduations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
