<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Security: My Journey to Becoming a Certified AppSec Practitioner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>February 13, 2024 marked a significant milestone in my professional journey as I successfully passed the Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) exam from The SecOps Group. This certification validates my expertise in application security, a field that has become increasingly critical in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
What is CAP? The CAP certification is a highly sought-after credential in the cybersecurity industry. It recognizes individuals who possess the knowledge and skills necessary to secure applications throughout their development lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Cyber Security Professional: Insights from a Bootcamp Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bughunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bughunter/</guid>
      <description>From Zero to Cyber Security Hero in One Month It&amp;rsquo;s been a whirlwind of a month, but I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I&amp;rsquo;ve just completed an intensive Cyber Security Bootcamp at SanberCode! This program was designed to transform individuals with no prior experience into skilled penetration testers and bug hunters. And let me tell you, it was an incredible journey.
What I Learned The bootcamp covered a wide range of topics, including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordera: Your Ultimate Destination for Seamless Food and Beverage Delivery in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ordera/</guid>
      <description>Ordera: Delivering Delicious Food to Your Doorstep! Have you ever craved a warm plate of fried rice on a cold night but felt too lazy to leave the house? Or wanted to try out new dishes from your favorite restaurant without having to wait in line?
Ordera is here to meet your needs!
Ordera: What Makes It Special? Ordera is a rising food and beverage delivery application in Indonesia. This app offers several advantages that make it a must-try:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building SITERPADU: Streamlining Academic Administration at Universitas Jenderal Achmad Yani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/siterpadu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/siterpadu/</guid>
      <description>Overview Greetings, fellow tech enthusiasts! Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share my journey as a Full Stack Developer at Bandung Techno Park, where I had the privilege of contributing to the development of the SITERPADU application. This project, spanning from January 1, 2022, to December 31, 2022, provided me with invaluable hands-on experience and a deeper understanding of the intricacies of full-stack development.
Delving into SITERPADU: A Comprehensive Academic Management System SITERPADU stands as a testament to the power of technology in streamlining academic administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Opening Doors to a Career in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>December 11, 2020, is a day I&amp;rsquo;ll always remember. On that date, I successfully passed the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This exam marked an important initial step in my journey toward becoming a proficient database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a COVID-19 WebGIS Application: Memorable Internship Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid19-webgis/</guid>
      <description>June - July 2020
Interning at PT Sketsa Negeri Mandiri in 2020 was no ordinary experience. Alongside one team member, I had the opportunity to contribute to an important project: building the COVID-19 WebGIS application.
What is COVID-19 WebGIS? Imagine an online platform displaying COVID-19 data in Indonesia visually, complete with maps, charts, and analysis. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s the COVID-19 WebGIS, a web-based application that helps users understand the pandemic situation better.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
