<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/grafana/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/grafana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Your New Application on OpenResty Edge: An Easy-to-Follow Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome aboard! If you’re gearing up to launch a new application on OpenResty Edge, you’re in the right place. Whether you’re a seasoned pro or just starting out, I’ll walk you through every step of the way with a dash of fun. Grab your favorite drink, settle in, and let’s dive into this setup adventure!
Creating Your New Application Alright, let’s get that shiny new application up and running.
Login to your OpenResty Edge Dashboard On the top bar, look for the Applications menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Ahead of Issues: How to Connect Grafana Alerts with Slack and Jira Using n8n</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</guid>
      <description>So, you’re ready to up your game and make sure you never miss a critical update? Great choice! Setting up Grafana alerts and integrating them with Slack and Jira through n8n is a powerful way to keep your team on the ball. Let’s dive in and get those workflows automated!
Setting Up Grafana Alerts First up, let’s get your Grafana alerts configured so you’re always in the know. Here’s the lowdown on how to get your alerts up and running:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
