<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Certificates on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/certificates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certificates on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Charting My Cyber Security Path: A Collection of Courses and Certifications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! Welcome to my cyber security collection. If you’re here, you probably share a love for all things tech and security like I do. Over time, I&amp;rsquo;ve dived into various courses and earned certifications that have shaped my journey in cyber security. Below is a showcase of what I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished so far, along with the skills I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up along the way.
Why Cyber Security? Let’s face it—cyber threats aren’t going anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>On December 11, 2020, I took an important step in my tech career by passing the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This milestone marked the beginning of my journey toward becoming a skilled database administrator, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more excited to share what I learned along the way.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? The MTA Database Administration Fundamentals certification is designed to test your basic knowledge and skills in database management.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
