<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Cloud Platform on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/google-cloud-platform/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google Cloud Platform on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/google-cloud-platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deploying T-Pot Honeypot on Google Cloud Platform (GCP)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/deploying-tpot-honeypot-on-gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/deploying-tpot-honeypot-on-gcp/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to explore security and dive into honeypot analysis, T-Pot is a fantastic tool that consolidates multiple honeypots into one robust platform. Today, I’ll guide you step-by-step through deploying T-Pot on Google Cloud Platform (GCP). By the end, you’ll have a fully operational T-Pot honeypot ready to capture and visualize attack data.
What is T-Pot? T-Pot, developed by T-Mobile, is an all-in-one honeypot platform supporting over 20 honeypots. It includes features like animated attack maps, visualization through Elastic Stack, and a suite of tools for enhanced threat analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Gophish on Google Cloud Platform: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</guid>
      <description>What is Gophish? Gophish is a powerful open-source phishing framework designed to make the process of conducting and managing phishing campaigns as straightforward as possible. Think of it as your go-to tool for simulating real-world phishing attacks. The best part? It&amp;rsquo;s free and easy to use!
Affordable: Gophish is open-source software, which means you don&amp;rsquo;t have to pay a cent to use it. Accessible: Written in the Go programming language, Gophish releases are compiled binaries with no dependencies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
