<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Charting My Cyber Security Path: A Collection of Courses and Certifications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! Welcome to my cyber security collection. If you’re here, you probably share a love for all things tech and security like I do. Over time, I&amp;rsquo;ve dived into various courses and earned certifications that have shaped my journey in cyber security. Below is a showcase of what I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished so far, along with the skills I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up along the way.
Why Cyber Security? Let’s face it—cyber threats aren’t going anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Your New Application on OpenResty Edge: An Easy-to-Follow Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-a-new-app-on-openresty-edge/</guid>
      <description>Welcome aboard! If you’re gearing up to launch a new application on OpenResty Edge, you’re in the right place. Whether you’re a seasoned pro or just starting out, I’ll walk you through every step of the way with a dash of fun. Grab your favorite drink, settle in, and let’s dive into this setup adventure!
Creating Your New Application Let&amp;rsquo;s get that new app live and kicking in no time. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to create your first application on OpenResty Edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Ahead of Issues: How to Connect Grafana Alerts with Slack and Jira Using n8n</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/integrating-grafana-slack-and-jira/</guid>
      <description>So, you’re ready to up your game and make sure you never miss a critical update? Great choice! Setting up Grafana alerts and integrating them with Slack and Jira through n8n is a powerful way to keep your team on the ball. Let’s dive in and get those workflows automated!
Setting Up Grafana Alerts First up, let’s get your Grafana alerts configured so you’re always in the know. Here’s the lowdown on how to get your alerts up and running:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Gophish on Google Cloud Platform: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/installing-gophish-on-gcp/</guid>
      <description>What is Gophish? Gophish is a powerful open-source phishing framework designed to make the process of conducting and managing phishing campaigns as straightforward as possible. Think of it as your go-to tool for simulating real-world phishing attacks. The best part? It&amp;rsquo;s free and easy to use!
Affordable: Gophish is open-source software, which means you don&amp;rsquo;t have to pay a cent to use it. Accessible: Written in the Go programming language, Gophish releases are compiled binaries with no dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Alerts to Malware: A CyberOps Associates v1.0 Skill Assessment Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-v1-0-skills-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-v1-0-skills-assessment/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered what security analysts actually do? Buckle up, because we&amp;rsquo;re diving into a thrilling investigation of a malware attack! Today&amp;rsquo;s culprit? The notorious Pushdo trojan.
This post will take you through a simulated security assessment, mimicking the thought process and steps involved in uncovering malicious activity. We&amp;rsquo;ll dissect alerts, explore the tools used for analysis, and ultimately expose the tricks employed by Pushdo.
So, grab a cup of coffee (or your beverage of choice), and let&amp;rsquo;s embark on this malware takedown adventure!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Like a Pro: A Beginner’s Guide to Vulnhub&#39;s Basic Pentesting 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to test your penetration testing skills in a safe environment? Look no further than Vulnhub&amp;rsquo;s Basic Pentesting 1 machine! This virtual machine is designed specifically for beginners like me, offering a controlled space to learn the ropes of exploiting vulnerabilities and gaining access.
In this guide, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the thrilling journey of taking down Basic Pentesting 1, step-by-step. So, grab your tools and get ready to unleash your inner hacker (for good, of course)!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Code: My Experience with Malware Analysis at Protergo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</guid>
      <description>During my technical interview at Protergo, I had the opportunity to showcase my skills in malware analysis. This blog post will take you through the exciting journey of dissecting a suspicious file using Cuckoo Sandbox, a powerful tool for both static and dynamic analysis.
Step-by-Step Malware Analysis with Cuckoo Sandbox Step 1: Unpacking the Suspect After downloading the sample file, I unzipped it to reveal its contents. This initial step allows us to see what&amp;rsquo;s lurking inside the archive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
