<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hacking a Vulnerable Website: A Step-by-Step (Unethical) Guide (For Educational Purposes Only!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vulnhub-basic-pentesting-1/</guid>
      <description>The Target: A Vulnhub Machine Meet the target: Vulnhub Basic Pentesting 1. This machine, released on December 8, 2017, is authored by Josiah Pierce as part of the Basic Pentesting series.
Finding the Target&amp;rsquo;s IP Address Identifying the Local IP I first need a starting point. My local IP address (like 192.168.100.9 in this example) acts as a launchpad for locating the target machine.
Netdiscover for IP Scouting I&amp;rsquo;ll likely use a tool like netdiscover to scan the network for active devices, revealing the target&amp;rsquo;s IP address (192.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Digital Landscape: An Introduction to Cybersecurity with Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s hyperconnected world, cybersecurity has become an indispensable skill, not just for tech professionals but for everyone navigating the digital landscape. With the ever-evolving nature of cyber threats, understanding the fundamentals of cybersecurity is crucial to safeguard our personal and professional lives.
Embarking on the Cybersecurity Path My fascination with cybersecurity led me to enroll in Cisco Networking Academy&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Cybersecurity course on February 28, 2024. This comprehensive course provided a solid foundation in the world of cybersecurity, equipping me with the knowledge and skills to navigate the digital frontier with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Security: Achieving Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) with The SecOps Group</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>February 13, 2024 marked a significant milestone in my professional journey as I successfully passed the Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) exam from The SecOps Group. This certification validates my expertise in application security, a field that has become increasingly critical in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
What is CAP? The CAP certification is a highly sought-after credential in the cybersecurity industry. It recognizes individuals who possess the knowledge and skills necessary to secure applications throughout their development lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security Exploration: Unveiling the Path to Becoming a Pentester and Bug Hunter with SanberCode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bug-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bug-hunter/</guid>
      <description>From Zero to Cyber Security Hero in One Month It&amp;rsquo;s been a whirlwind of a month, but I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I&amp;rsquo;ve just completed an intensive Cyber Security Bootcamp at SanberCode! This program was designed to transform individuals with no prior experience into skilled penetration testers and bug hunters. And let me tell you, it was an incredible journey.
What I Learned The bootcamp covered a wide range of topics, including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening Cyber Defenses: My Growth with ITBOX&#39;s Cybersecurity Courses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-security-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-security-courses/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered how those hackers manage to break into secure systems and steal valuable data? Or perhaps you&amp;rsquo;re fascinated by the intricate world of cybersecurity and want to learn how to protect yourself from online threats? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently embarked on an exciting journey into the realm of cybersecurity, and I&amp;rsquo;m here to share my experience with you.
Embarking on the Cybersecurity Path My cybersecurity adventure began on January 02, 2024, when I enrolled in the Cyber Security Course Level Basic from ITBOX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Code: My Experience with Malware Analysis at Protergo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/malware-analysis-protergo/</guid>
      <description>During my technical interview at Protergo, I had the opportunity to showcase my skills in malware analysis. This blog post will take you through the exciting journey of dissecting a suspicious file using Cuckoo Sandbox, a powerful tool for both static and dynamic analysis.
Step-by-Step Malware Analysis with Cuckoo Sandbox Unpacking the Suspect After downloading the sample file, I unzipped it to reveal its contents. This initial step allows us to see what&amp;rsquo;s lurking inside the archive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
