<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Certificates on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/certificates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certificates on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Charting My Cyber Security Path: A Collection of Courses and Certifications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-collection-of-courses-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! Welcome to my cyber security collection. If you’re here, you probably share a love for all things tech and security like I do. Over time, I&amp;rsquo;ve dived into various courses and earned certifications that have shaped my journey in cyber security. Below is a showcase of what I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished so far, along with the skills I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up along the way.
Why Cyber Security? Let’s face it—cyber threats aren’t going anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>On December 11, 2020, I took a significant step in my tech journey by passing the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This achievement marked the start of my quest to become a skilled database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:
Topic Description Basic database concepts Understanding database structure and terminology Database creation and management Creating, managing, and maintaining databases Database security Implementing security measures to protect databases Troubleshooting and problem-solving Identifying and resolving database issues Why Did I Pursue This Certification?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
