<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Certificates on Tomi Mulhartono</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/certificates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certificates on Tomi Mulhartono</description>
    <image>
      <title>Tomi Mulhartono</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Career Essentials in Cybersecurity: My Journey with Microsoft and LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/career-essentials-in-cybersecurity-by-microsoft-and-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/career-essentials-in-cybersecurity-by-microsoft-and-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, cyber enthusiasts! I’m stoked to share my recent adventure into the world of cybersecurity. I just wrapped up the Career Essentials in Cybersecurity by Microsoft and LinkedIn learning path, and let me tell you, it was a rollercoaster ride of knowledge and excitement.
I’m breaking down my experience and the awesome courses I conquered in this post. Let’s dive in!
The Cybersecurity Threat Landscape: More Than Just a Scary Headline Remember those heart-stopping news stories about massive data breaches and mind-boggling hacks?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Networks with Wireshark: From Packet Zero to Network Hero with David Bombal and Chris Greer on Udemy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/getting-started-with-wireshark-the-ultimate-hands-on-course-udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/getting-started-with-wireshark-the-ultimate-hands-on-course-udemy/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, fellow network enthusiasts and cybersecurity aficionados! I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share my recent triumph in the realm of network analysis, having successfully completed the Getting Started with Wireshark: The Ultimate Hands-On Course from Udemy. This comprehensive course, masterfully guided by instructors David Bombal and Chris Greer, equipped me with the essential skills to navigate the intricate world of network traffic and unravel its mysteries.
Delving into the Depths of Network Traffic My journey commenced with a thorough understanding of the fundamentals of network traffic capture and interpretation using Wireshark, the industry-standard network protocol analyzer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberOps Odyssey: My Path to Mastery in the Digital Talent Scholarship 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-professional-academy-digital-talent-scholarship-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyberops-associate-professional-academy-digital-talent-scholarship-2024/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving realm of cybersecurity, staying ahead of the curve is crucial. As cyber threats become more sophisticated, the need for skilled professionals to combat them grows ever stronger. This is where the Digital Talent Scholarship 2024 from the Pusbang Proserti (Center for Professional Development and Certification), an agency under the Ministry of Communication and Information (Kominfo) Indonesia, stepped in.
I had the privilege of participating in their CyberOps Associate training program, a Cisco-partnered initiative designed to equip individuals with the essential skills and knowledge to defend against cyberattacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Novice to Network Pro: Unleashing CCNA 200-301 with David Bombal on Udemy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cisco-ccna-packet-tracer-ultimate-labs-ccna-200-301-udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cisco-ccna-packet-tracer-ultimate-labs-ccna-200-301-udemy/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving realm of technology, networking has emerged as a cornerstone of modern infrastructure. With the increasing demand for skilled network professionals, the Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) certification stands as a coveted credential that validates one&amp;rsquo;s expertise in designing, implementing, and managing network systems.
My passion for networking led me to embark on a journey to attain the CCNA certification. To equip myself with the necessary skills and knowledge, I enrolled in the Cisco CCNA Packet Tracer Ultimate Labs: CCNA 200-301 labs course on Udemy, instructed by the esteemed David Bombal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Cyber Vigilance: Cisco&#39;s Cyber Threat Management Course Explored</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-threat-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-threat-management/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, cybersecurity has become paramount for individuals and organizations alike. With the ever-evolving threat landscape, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to stay ahead of the curve and equip ourselves with the knowledge and skills to combat cyber threats effectively. Recently, I embarked on a journey to enhance my cybersecurity expertise by enrolling in Cisco Networking Academy&amp;rsquo;s Cyber Threat Management course. This comprehensive course provided me with a deep dive into the intricacies of cybersecurity, equipping me with the tools and strategies to navigate the complex world of cyber threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying the Secrets of Ancient Codes: A Beginner&#39;s Journey into Classical Cryptography with Cyber Academy Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/classical-cryptography-for-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/classical-cryptography-for-beginner/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, where information is currency and security is paramount, cryptography has become an indispensable tool. But have you ever wondered how the ancient world kept their secrets safe long before computers and complex algorithms? Embark on a captivating journey into the realm of classical cryptography, where we&amp;rsquo;ll unravel the ingenious methods used to encode and decode messages, ensuring their confidentiality even in the face of prying eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Digital Landscape: My Journey into Introduction to Information Security with Cyber Academy Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-information-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-information-security/</guid>
      <description>Hello fellow tech enthusiasts and cybersecurity aficionados! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my recent foray into the fascinating world of cybersecurity through Cyber Academy Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Information Security online course. Buckle up as I take you on a journey through my learning experience and the key takeaways I gained from this informative course.
Diving into the Fundamentals of Cybersecurity The course kicked off with a comprehensive introduction to cybersecurity, delving into the intricacies of this ever-evolving domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Digital Realm: My Journey Through Cisco&#39;s Endpoint Security Course</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/endpoint-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/endpoint-security/</guid>
      <description>As the digital landscape continues to expand, so does the threat of cyberattacks. With an ever-increasing number of devices accessing sensitive data, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to have robust security measures in place to protect our networks and endpoints. That&amp;rsquo;s why I recently embarked on a journey to enhance my cybersecurity expertise by taking Cisco Networking&amp;rsquo;s Endpoint Security course.
Navigating the Cybersecurity Landscape The course provided me with a comprehensive understanding of the various security threats that organizations face today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Cyberspace: A Dive into Ethical Hacker Training with Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ethical-hacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ethical-hacker/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my blog! The digital world is rapidly evolving, opening up new opportunities while also presenting increasingly complex cybersecurity risks. On March 29, 2024, I completed the Ethical Hacker course from Cisco Networking Academy, a significant step in my journey to becoming a hero in this challenging digital landscape.
What is Ethical Hacking? Ethical hacking is the practice of learning and applying hacking techniques used by malicious hackers, but with the noble purpose of finding and fixing system vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Kickstarted My Career in Cybersecurity: A Sharing Session with Merdeka Siber Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-kick-starting-career-into-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-kick-starting-career-into-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my experience attending the &amp;ldquo;How To Kick Starting Career Into Cyber Security&amp;rdquo; sharing session hosted by Merdeka Siber Academy on March 24, 2024. This insightful session provided me with valuable knowledge about the fundamentals of SOC Analyst roles and the exciting prospects of career shifting into cybersecurity.
Topic Key Points SOC Analyst Role Monitoring, analyzing, and responding to security incidents to safeguard sensitive data and critical infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Digital Landscape: An Introduction to Cybersecurity with Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction-to-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s hyperconnected world, cybersecurity has become an indispensable skill, not just for tech professionals but for everyone navigating the digital landscape. With the ever-evolving nature of cyber threats, understanding the fundamentals of cybersecurity is crucial to safeguard our personal and professional lives.
Embarking on the Cybersecurity Path My fascination with cybersecurity led me to enroll in Cisco Networking Academy&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Cybersecurity course on February 28, 2024. This comprehensive course provided a solid foundation in the world of cybersecurity, equipping me with the knowledge and skills to navigate the digital frontier with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Security: Achieving Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) with The SecOps Group</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/certified-appsec-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>February 13, 2024 marked a significant milestone in my professional journey as I successfully passed the Certified AppSec Practitioner (CAP) exam from The SecOps Group. This certification validates my expertise in application security, a field that has become increasingly critical in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
What is CAP? The CAP certification is a highly sought-after credential in the cybersecurity industry. It recognizes individuals who possess the knowledge and skills necessary to secure applications throughout their development lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security Exploration: Unveiling the Path to Becoming a Pentester and Bug Hunter with SanberCode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bug-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pentester-and-bug-hunter/</guid>
      <description>From Zero to Cyber Security Hero in One Month It&amp;rsquo;s been a whirlwind of a month, but I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I&amp;rsquo;ve just completed an intensive Cyber Security Bootcamp at SanberCode! This program was designed to transform individuals with no prior experience into skilled penetration testers and bug hunters. And let me tell you, it was an incredible journey.
What I Learned The bootcamp covered a wide range of topics, including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening Cyber Defenses: My Growth with ITBOX&#39;s Cybersecurity Courses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-security-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cyber-security-courses/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered how those hackers manage to break into secure systems and steal valuable data? Or perhaps you&amp;rsquo;re fascinated by the intricate world of cybersecurity and want to learn how to protect yourself from online threats? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently embarked on an exciting journey into the realm of cybersecurity, and I&amp;rsquo;m here to share my experience with you.
Embarking on the Cybersecurity Path My cybersecurity adventure began on January 02, 2024, when I enrolled in the Cyber Security Course Level Basic from ITBOX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Administration Fundamentals: Key to Unlocking Opportunities in Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/database-administration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>December 11, 2020, is a day I&amp;rsquo;ll always remember. On that date, I successfully passed the Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) certification exam for Database Administration Fundamentals. This exam marked an important initial step in my journey toward becoming a proficient database administrator.
What is Database Administration Fundamentals? Database Administration Fundamentals is an MTA certification designed to validate basic knowledge and skills in database administration. This certification covers various topics, including:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
